Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1961-1984, I.; Item 1-123
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 073, 1961/1984, 1 5 inch reel; Container title: Diabelskie Skrzypce Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: unknown Title scribbled on leader of tape: Diabelskie skrzypce; this is possibly from a June 30 1978 performance at Festival Nieuwe Muziek, Middelburg, Netherlands, but Uitti and Mikhashoff also performed on other programs 1 file, 1 work Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 73)
    Contents: Hiller: Diabelskie skrzypce
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_073_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_073_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_073_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 074, 1961/1984, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Constellation / Yoshio Hachimura Performers: Unknown Recording location: unknown There is a Toshiba EMI label on the container making it likely that this is the performance from that commercially available recording. It may contain a 2nd work, One hour at every one breath and possibly two works on the original Toshiba LP by Shuko Mizuno: Provisional colour and Autonomy of voice; Photocopy of printed program for December 16 1978 concert in the Evenings for New Music series performed by Mikhashoff, piano; Weronika Knittel, violin; Jan Williams, tubular bells; Michael Pugliese, vibraphone at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery 1 file, 1 work Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 74)
    Contents: Hachimura: Constellation
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_074_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_074_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_074_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 075, 1978-10-09, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Hartt PF Recital 1978 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Millard Auditorium, Hartt College of Music, University of Hartford Photocopy of printed program inserted; World premières: Mirrors VII, Sonetti d'Ebe; US premières: Gran duo, Separate ways, To the master; dedicated to Mikhashoff and Uitti: Separate ways Derivative files created: 5 (Box 6, Item 75)
    Contents: Bussotti: Gran duo, da Beethoven; Diemente: Mirrors VII; Evangelisti: Proporzione; Sellars: Separate ways; Franchetti: Sonetti d'Ebe; Scelsi: To the master; Stravinsky: Suite italien
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_075_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_075_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_075_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_075_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_075_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_075_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_075_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_075_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_075_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_075_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_075_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_075_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 076, 1978-11-24, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Italian Visionaries (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 1 of 4 No program located and date not verified (see Tape 70 container back); contents split amongst Tapes 76-79 Requires checking: 2 files Derivative files created: 2 (Box 6, Item 76)
    Contents: Possible contents: Scelsi: To the master -- TTAI 1 and 2; Mikhashoff: spoken introduction for Bussotti works; Bussotti: Solo selon Sade -- Musica per amici - Illustazione -- Sensitivo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_076_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_076_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_076_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_076_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_076_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 077, 24 November 1978?, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Italian Visionaries (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 2 of 4 No program located and date not verified (see Tape 70 container back); contents split amongst Tapes 76-79 Requires checking: Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 77)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_077_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_077_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_077_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_077_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_077_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_077_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_077_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 078, 1978-11-24, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Italian Visionaries (3) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 3 of 4 No program located and date not verified (see Tape 70 container back); contents split amongst Tapes 76-79 Derivative files created: 2 (Box 6, Item 78)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_078_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_078_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_078_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_078_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_078_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 079, 1978-11-24, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Italian Visionaries (4) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 4 of 4 No program located and date not verified (see Tape 70 container back); contents split amongst Tapes 76-79 Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 79)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_079_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_079_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_079_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_079_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_079_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_079_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_079_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 080, 1978-05-10, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Live from Studio A … Liszt, Sonata in b Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Tape may be flipped, oxide side out Program from label on container back Includes spoken introduction Derivative files created: 1 (Box 6, Item 80)
    Contents: Liszt: Sonata in b
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_080_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_080_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_080_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 081, 1978-01-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Louisiana Museum, Denmark (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Louisiana Museum, Fredensborg, Denmark Reel 1 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted Derivative files created: 5 (Box 6, Item 81)
    Contents: Brown: December 1952; Cowell: The banshee; Feldman: Intersection IV; Davidovsky: Synchronisms no.6; Feldman: Durations 2
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_081_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_081_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_081_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_081_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_081_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_081_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_081_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_081_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_081_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_081_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_081_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 082, 1978-01-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Louisiana Museum, Denmark (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Louisiana Museum, Fredensborg, Denmark Reel 2 of 2 Printed program inserted in Tape 81 Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 82)
    Contents: Wolff: Prose collection; Sellars: Sonata for piano; Cage: Concerto for piano and cello, with Fontana Mix
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_082_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_082_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_082_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_082_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_082_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_082_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_082_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 083, 1978-12-13, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Prokofiev (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 1 of 4 Title of program on Tape 86 container: 1953-1978, In memoriam S. Prokofiev, WBFO, 13 Dec. 1978; no printed program located Derivative files created: 4 (Box 6, Item 83)
    Contents: Prokofiev: specific works not stated
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_083_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_083_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_083_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_083_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_083_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_083_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_083_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_083_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_083_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 084, 1978-12-13, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Prokofiev (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano, and violinist Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 2 of 4 Title of program on Tape 86 container: 1953-1978, In memoriam S. Prokofiev, WBFO, 13 Dec. 1978; no printed program located Derivative files created: 4 (Box 6, Item 84)
    Contents: Prokofiev: unspecified works
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_084_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_084_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_084_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_084_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_084_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_084_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_084_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_084_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_084_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 085, 1978-12-13, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Prokofiev (3) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 3 of 4 Title of program on Tape 86 container: 1953-1978, In memoriam S. Prokofiev, WBFO, 13 Dec. 1978; no printed program located Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 85)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_085_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_085_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_085_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_085_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_085_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_085_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_085_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 086, 1978-12-13, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1978 Prokofiev (4) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Reel 4 of 4 Title of program on Tape 86 container: 1953-1978, In memoriam S. Prokofiev, WBFO, 13 Dec. 1978; no printed program located Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 86)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_086_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_086_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_086_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_086_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_086_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_086_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_086_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 087, 1978, Tape is missing; Tape is missing but was described during the original processing. Container title: 1978 WBFO Studio 2 recording Performers: Mikhashoff (Box 6, Item 87)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 088, 1979-10-18, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: H. Johnson - Sonata Master #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Robert Dick, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Lesley Delk, soprano; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Photocopy of printed program inserted; it is not clear whether the tape contains the entire concert program: Retrospective II: The Music of Hunter Johnson, or only the Piano sonata; See also correspondence between Hunter Johnson and Mikhashoff Derivative files created: 2 (Box 6, Item 88)
    Contents: Johnson, Hunter: Three songs of Emily Dickinson -- Trio -- Serenade -- Piano sonata
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_088_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_088_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_088_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_088_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_088_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_088_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_088_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 089, 1979-10-18, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: H. Johnson Sonata master #2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Robert Dick, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Lesley Delk, soprano; Deborah Ungaro, clarinet Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Photocopy of printed program inserted in Tape 88; it is not clear whether the tape contains the entire concert program or only the Piano sonata; this reel could be a continuation of Tape 88 or a 2nd copy of it Derivative files created: 1 (Box 6, Item 89)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_089_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_089_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_089_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_089_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_089_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 090, 1979-11-18, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1979 Feldman "Piano 1977" Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Recital Hall Box is signed YM with date of 18 November 1979, date of the Evenings for New Music concert in Baird Recital Hall; conflicts with date given in concert announcement (inserted) Derivative files created: 1 (Box 6, Item 90)
    Contents: Feldman: Piano (1977)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_090_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_090_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_090_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 091, 1961/1984, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Fall of Usher Performers: Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Mikhashoff, piano; other performers Recording location: Unknown Check contents - see comments The original processor identified this as being a recording of John Cage's Fontana Mix, performed 16 April 1980 at Baird Recital Hall. There is no indication on the container for this. Derivative files created: 3 (Box 6, Item 91)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Fall of the House of Usher
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_091_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_091_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_091_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 092, 1980-03-04, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Foss - Solo; Scelsi - Quartet no. IV Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; others Recording location: KRO [Catholic Radio Station], Hilversum, Netherlands Broadcast 4 March 1980, 20:00 to 21:10 hrs from KRO Hilversum Derivative files created: 9 (Box 7, Item 92)
    Contents: Foss: Solo; Scelsi: Quartet no. IV
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_092_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_092_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_092_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_092_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_092_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_092_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_092_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 093, 1980-02-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1980 Uitti - Mikhashoff 1920's / Reh. (0) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Note on container: "Recording - practice 2/22/80" - these are takes from the rehearsal; contents as transcribed from container - this differs from what was described by the original processor. Photocopy of printed program for concert inserted Derivative files created: 4 (Box 7, Item 93)
    Contents: Debussy: La puerta del vino (played twice?) -- General Lavine -- Danseuses des Delphes -- Minstrels; Krenek: Ballad and tango; Milhaud: Sumare; Smit: Pochoirs
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_093_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_093_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_093_01-09pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_093_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_093_01-09sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 094, 1980-02-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1980 Uitti - Mikhashoff 1920's / Radio (1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Check contents Note on container: "Broadcast - air check, Part I, 2/22/80"; contents from container - there are discrepancies between contents stated on container versus what the original processor stated, based on the printed program for the 2/24/80 concert titled The Musical world of Sonia Delaunay. Krenek and Debussy transcribed by Mikhashoff and Uitti; see also items 93, 95 Derivative files created: 3 (Box 7, Item 94)
    Contents: Stravinksy: Suite Italienne -- Introduzione; Krenek: Ballad and tango (Jonny); Milhaud: Sumare; Debussy: La puerta del vino
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_094_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_094_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_094_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_094_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_094_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_094_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_094_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_094_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_094_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 095, 1980-02-22, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1980 Uitti - Mikhashoff 1920's / Radio (2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Recording location: Buffalo radio station, WBFO Check contents Note on container: "Broadcast air-check, Part II - 2/22/80". Contents from container - there are discrepancies between contents stated on container versus what the original processor stated, based on the printed program for the 2/24/80 concert titled The Musical world of Sonia Delaunay. World première: Delaunay poichoirs; dedicated to Mikhashoff and Uitti: Delaunay pochoirs; see also items 93, 94 Derivative files created: 1 (Box 7, Item 95)
    Contents: Debussy: General Lavine - eccentric -- Danseuses de Delphes; Smit: Delaunay pochoirs
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_095_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_095_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_095_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_095_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_095_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_095_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_095_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 096, 1980-01-08, 1 3 inch reel; Container title: 1980 Vigeland - Piano Sonata Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Danish Radio, collaboration with Dut, Copenhague, Denmark Annotation on container: "use 3rd take (w/o pedal version)" - unclear if this means there are multiple takes on the tape Derivative files created: 8 (Box 7, Item 96)
    Contents: Vigeland: Piano sonata (Piano II - conclusion)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_096_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_096_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_096_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 097, 1981-03-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1981 Copland concert #2 (Tape #1) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano; Gary Burgess, tenor; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: Albany Institute, Albany, New York Tape appears to have been re-used - check for bleedthrough or remnants of earlier content On container: "Copland Festival Concert 2 (Tape 1) Auric -- Roussel (Intro) .. With commentary. Festival titled Portrait of Aaron Copland. An anniversary tribute for his 80th year. Four concerts sponsored by Cambiata, Inc. in cooperation with The Albany Institute of History and Art, with the composer in attendance. March 20, 21, 22. Concert titled Copland and Paris (1921-1981). Continued on Tape 98-99 Derivative files created: 7 (Box 7, Item 97)
    Contents: Auric: Adieu, New York; Copland: The cat and the mouse -- Old poem -- Pastorale; Villa-Lobos: Sertaneja; Fauré: Diane -- Selene; Ravel: Berceuse; Roussel: Finale
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_097_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_097_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_097_01-08pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_097_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_097_01-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 098, 1981-03-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1981 Copland Concert #2 (Tape #2) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano; Gary Burgess, tenor; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: Albany Institute, Albany, New York Continuation of Tape 97. Note on back of container: Roussel (Adagio) from Sonata, [Copland] Passacaglia announced but not played (Leo Smit); notes on container include comments on quality of performances; Derivative files created: 9 (Box 7, Item 98)
    Contents: Roussel: Finale; Milhaud: Passacaglia; Satie: Ludions; Ravel: Blues; Stravinsky: Finale; Poulenc: Poème de Ronsard
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_098_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_098_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_098_01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_098_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_098_01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 099, 1981-03-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1981 Copland Concert #2 (Tape #3) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Leo Smit, piano; Gary Burgess, tenor; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: Albany Institute, Albany, New York End of concert no.2 titled Copland and Paris (1921-1981) and beginning of concert no.3 titled Copland and Smit; Continuation of Tape 97-98 and continued on Tape 100 Derivative files created: 2 (Box 7, Item 99)
    Contents: Auric: B.; Copland: Poet's Song -- Dirge in Woods -- Sentimental Melody -- Blues No. IV -- Nocturne -- Ukulele Serenade -- Prelude -- Old American songs, set 1. Boatman's song
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_099_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_099_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_099_01-09pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_099_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_099_01-09sc.mp3